Hamza Tahir

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



CONTACT

0

+92 320 2112565



hamtah112@gmail.com



www.webarchitectslab.com



hamzatahir.netlify.com

EDUCATION

2017-2021

City University, London

Bachelor Degree of Computer Science , HND

SKILLS (TECHNICAL)

- HTML, CSS, JS
- RAECTJS, Next js
- Laravel, Nodejs
- Github, Jira, Bitbucket
- Context Api, Redux toolkit, hooks.
- MYsql, mongodb.
- Extensive experience with MUI AND Restful apis.

Skills(non-Technical)

- Above average communication skills (English).
- Team player.

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am Hamza Tahir a designated Front-end web developer from Pakistan with over 2 years of relevant experience in industry. I tends to give my best in the field of software development as I desired to become the best software developer. Working with the coordination of the team to complete the project is one of my strenght.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVBELOPER (REACT/NEXT)

Ginkgo Retail

April 2022 - Present

- · Building frontends for their web based products
- Works with the collaboration of backend developers
- Server side rendering with nextjs
- Making mobile responsive design following figma

FULL STACK DEVELOPER (LARAVEL+REACT)

Shayan Pakistan

Nov 2021 - April 2022

- Work on their different projects on their property based projects
- Works as a team lead developer
- managing the road map for new internees as well as working as a full stack

WEBSITE MANAGER

al aziz laptop parts

Nov 2020 - Sep2021

- Worked on to manage their website
- Worked to modify frontend with HTML,CSS, JS
- managing their clients and data on ms excel

WEBSITE DEVELOPER

Orionfirm Lahore

6months

- Worked on to manage their website
- Here i learned HTML,CSS BOOTSTRAP AND wordpress